itweetpic.com 2011-09-02

# iTweetpic.com Privacy

## Privacy Policy 

Effective as of July 1st, 2011 

iTweetpic.com allows users to upload images with a unique URL to create online access to the images for themselves and others, both on the Site and on other websites where the user posts the URL. 

The Site is a general audience site and iTweetpic does not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age and children under 13 are not allowed to use this site. 

By visiting the iTweetpic website located at www.iTweetpic.com and any linked pages, features, content, or application services offered from time to time by iTweetpic in connection therewith (the “Site”) and using iTweetpic services (the “Services”), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that iTweetpic does not own or control, including but not limited to third party services you access though iTweetpic, or to individuals that iTweetpic does not employ or manage. 

Your full user twitter name and your photo, if you decide to upload one, are displayed to people on the iTweetpic Site. 

When you visit iTweetpic, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We use data to monitor the use of the Site and of our Service, and for the Site's technical administration. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the Terms of Service 

Cookies 

A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. iTweetpic may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our Services. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our Service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. 

We may allow advertisers, third party advertising networks and third-party advertising serving companies to serve advertisements directly to you within iTweetpic's Sites, Services and Software. By serving these advertisements directly to you, these companies can set their own cookies on your computer. 

Advertisements 

The Services may include the use of ad banner partners for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions, and other marketing messages. These ads may be provided, in some cases, by a third party ad service provider. The ad service provider may place or utilize their own unique cookie on your browser, and may use non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our sites, such as the number of times you have viewed the ad. iTweetpic is not responsible for the collection of these cookies and is not responsible for the actions of the ad service providers. iTweetpic does not sponsor, endorse or guarantee any products or services advertised by third parties on its site. 

Sharing and Disclosure 

Information about our users is important to our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only as described below. 

Service Providers 

We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data. 

These companies may use information about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Your Post 

When you post a pic through iTweetpic, information about you, including user profile information, may be visible to other users. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, that information becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others and redistributed through the internet and other media channels. You may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Business Transfers 

In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if iTweetpic, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that iTweetpic goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred to or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of iTweetpic may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement 

iTweetpic cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of iTweetpic or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law. 

Non-US Users 

If you are not a resident of the United States, you understand and agree that iTweetpic stores and processes your information on computers located in the United States, and by providing any data to iTweetpic, you consent to the transfer of such information to the United States. 

Links to Other Websites 

The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. 

Children under 13 

The Site is not directed to persons under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our system. 

Contact 

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or information that you have submitted to us you can contact us at: 

Email: 

privacy@itweetpic.com
